(Sheldon:)Lady things.
(Amy:)Listen to me.
(Amy:)That is not the way
they usually look.
It doesn't matter.
(Sheldon:)This is no way
to make new humans.
(Sheldon:)People coming out of people.
(Sheldon:)It's some kind of dirty magic show.
(Mrs Cooper(off):)Sheldon Lee Cooper.
(Mrs Cooper(off):)You get back
in this room right now.
(Mrs Cooper(off):)And bring a mop.
(Sheldon:)Did you hear that?
(Mrs Cooper(off):)A mop.
(Sheldon:)I have two PhDs yet
somehow I'm the janitor
(Sheldon:)of my sister's birth canal.
(Leonard:)Hey, Sheldon sent us all
an e-mail.
"Happy holidays from Texas."
(Leonard:)And there's pictures.
(Leonard:)Ah! Don't open them.
Do not open them.
(Penny:)Oh, come on.
Childbirth is a natural, beautiful--